Henry William Herschel Crofts

17 Maltings Drive, Harleston, Norfolk, IP20 9EY 01379 853921 • 07432201220 • hwcrofts@gmail.com

Personal statement

A current computer games programming student expecting to graduate in 2019 from the University of Suffolk, with 3 years of experience using Unity3D and C# to develop games and applications for mobile and PC. Currently looking to secure a Unity Game Developer position or similar within a small team to utilise and build upon my current C# programming, communication and managerial skills within a practical and creative environment.

My eventual career goal is to assume responsibility of a small team within a company that values employee progression while working to develop a successful title.

Education

University of Suffolk

(September 2016 – Present)

(Grade) BSc. (Honours) Computer Games Programming

Key Skills gained:

- Developed games and applications to PC and mobile devices using Unity3D.
- Ability to debug, and structure code efficiently.
- Ability to work in small teams as well as manage those teams in an agile environment using Atlassian's JIRA
- Advanced problem solving.
- The use of version control software such as GitHub.
- Proficiency in the use of Microsoft Word, PowerPoint and Visual Studio.
- Good knowledge of Artificial Intelligence in games, as demonstrated by my Final Project.
- Proficient in the use of C# while familiar with C++.
- Accomplished communication skills, both written and verbal, developed through numerous essays and presentations.

Notable Modules - Managing Games Production, Group Project, Design Master Class & Final Project

Great Yarmouth College

(September 2012 – May 2013)

Level 3 BTEC Diploma in Information Technology – MERIT/MERIT Level 2 Photography - PASS

City College Norwich

(September 2011 – May 2012)

Level 3 BTEC Diploma in Sport and Exercise Science - MERIT/PASS

Archbishop Sancroft High School

(September 2006 – June 2011)

10 GCSEs, grade A*-C including Maths and English

Work Experience

General Labourer, Whartons PLC. Pulham St. Mary, Norfolk.

(September 2013 – August 2016)

Duties include:

- Working as a team to harvest the rose crop.
- Prepare rose crop to be sent out for orders.
- Bud rose bushes for the following year's crop.
- Preparing bushes for harvest in the winter, trimming, weeding.

Key results:

- Developed communication skills by working with different teams to ensure orders are completed on time.
- Worked with small teams across multiple departments.
 - o Gained Counterbalance and Tractor tickets.
 - o Trained specialist budder.
 - o Employed for summer seasonal work as a patcher between 2011-2013.

Hobbies & Interests

I am very passionate about video games. During 2009 – 2012 I was part of an online gaming community called Tactical Gaming, for the Gears of War division where I went on to become the Commanding Officer for the European brigade.

References

References are available on request.